Before a medical appointment
the hardest part is often
not a single symptom
It is remembering
the full story clearly
ClinDiary is a local-first
mobile diary for
daily health context
It is not an AI doctor
It is a private memory
layer that helps users
organize what
happened between visits
The user starts with
a voice check-in
They speak in English
review the transcript
and send it to Gemma
Gemma drafts the check-in
from what the user actually said
sleep, mood, stress
hydration and pain
notes and daily signals
If symptoms are mentioned
Gemma can add symptom drafts
with severity from zero to ten
duration and body location
The user stays in control
unclear details can remain empty
Gemma can ask questions
and everything is reviewed
before saving
The goal is not
to diagnose the symptom
It is to preserve details
usually forgotten
Medication context
can be tracked too
including schedules
adherence context and reminders
but ClinDiary does not prescribe medications
or suggest dosage changes
Documents can be stored
in an encrypted local vault
on the device
keeping important health context
close to the user
Ask Files searches
local document context
and shows cited snippets
so answers stay grounded
in what was actually saved
When the model is available
Gemma can help summarize
and explain local context
with cautious instructions
and clear safety boundaries
The app exposes the active AI path
including provider and runtime
model status and cloud-use proof
Daily, weekly, monthly
and pre-visit recaps
turn local entries into
readable summaries
users can review
Safety logic stays conservative
Prevention reminders are rule-based
discussion prompts
not AI decisions
about diagnosis or emergencies
The goal is simple
less forgotten context
more prepared conversations
and privacy by default
ClinDiary is a memory
layer for health
powered by local data and
Gemma-assisted summaries